We also have texts in the photo editor, so in text we can basically add text or use these text
combinations. So I wait until they are loaded. And as you see, over here we have plenty of preset
text designs that we can add to our project and edit them. So we have holiday. As you see,
we have them. We, I can click on more and more presets will be loaded for me. I can add subtitles,
text effects, you know, text group, promotion, tag, you know, and you can use any of them that
you want in your design or you can just click on add text in order to add a very simple one.
So a text box will be added over here. I can type something in it. I can say the take of
college, for example, right? And then using this very button over here, I'll be able to move my text.
What else do we have? We have phone family, as you see, setable from here. And we can just click on
any of them that we want. We also have phone size, which is changeable. We have phones color,
you know, we have text alignments inside the very text box that it's in. As you see, we'll be,
we'll be able to align it. As well as bold, italic, you know, upper case, underline, and all of
these text formatting options. And we can, we can highlight our text and we can also use transparency
option. So it's about, yeah, it's about the opacity of that very layer of us or that very text.
And after all, we'll be able to exit the text tool and then come here and select and move it
as easy as that, right? So I place it over here. I again, increase the phone size. No, it's a lot. This
is okay, for example. And yes, I place it over here as easy as that, right?